So it's Friday night.
I'm a young college student at this time. I'm attending a party at another university.
I'm making my way through this party...
...and I notice that there's this guy standing
a distance away from me, and he's just staring at me.
I don't pay it any attention. I keep doing my thing.
Every now and then, I look up and the guy is a little bit closer--still staring at me.
I still don't pay it any attention.
At one point, I'm talking to someone when suddenly, I hear these words behind me:
"What did you say?"
I turned around and it's this guy--standing right in my face.
I turned back around to look at the guy that I was talking to
to see if he was talking to him by any chance
and then I turned back to look at him.
And I was like "Are you talking to me?"
And he was like "Yeah! What did you say?"
And I was like "I didn't say anything to you."
And as soon as I said that, this guy takes his fist and *BOOM*--right in my face.
My head snaps back.
And I'm like--
--I don't respond.
I look around and I suddenly notice
that he's got his friends surrounding me -- I estimate probably 20 of them.
And I'm thinking to myself "Things are about to go down."
"This is not good."